Contact

+44 (0) 7305 818 593 tirsog@gmail.com Cheltenham, UK

Skills and Expertise

- · Product Management
- Project Management
- Digital Marketing
- Development (Junior PERN)
- Intellectual Property

Tools

- · Jira, Trello, Confluence, GitHub
- Zendesk, Google Admin, Google Sheets
- · Analytics, SEMRush
- · Figma, Lighthouse
- React, NextJS, Node, Tailwind, PostgreSQL, Express

Languages

- Spanish (Native)
- English (Bilingual)



<u>Linkedin</u>



Github



tirsoq.es

Tirso Garcia

Senior Product Manager

I'm a highly motivated, well rounded professional with experience of working in nearly every area of an e-commerce business. A high performer with an entrepreneurial spirit, I offer a strong background in project management, a wide breadth of knowledge of analytical tools and processes combined with a practical focus on delivery.

Experience



iGERENT - Global Trademark and IP Services

Feb 2015 - Present

Co-Founder

Founded international intellectual property services company in 2015 alongside two partners. Created the company strategy from scratch, participating in all aspects of business development, with a particular focus on marketing and finances. CEO/Managing Director until 2022, when we reorganised internal functions.

Some of the key achievements of the business over the last 9 years include: over 20,000 unique visitors per month in a very niche market, an average revenue of \$1.2m USD annually, over 2000 clients acquired, and a portfolio of over 10,000 trademarks managed in 160 countries.

Responsible for delivering the company's services and developing and executing marketing strategies, including by:

- Managing a team of 8+ devs and designers worldwide.
- Managing and executing projects for the Customer Support Team.
- Analysing, defining and taking new features into production.
- · Overseeing the company's pricing strategy.
- · Overseeing SEM, SEO and SMO.
- Running a 10k USD/mo SEM Budget.



Marcaria.com - Domain & Trademarks

Apr 2013 - Feb 2015

Marketing Analyst

Sept 2014 - Feb 2015

Responsible for collecting and analyzing marketing data and client behavior. Identifying trends, measuring the effectiveness of marketing strategies, and making recommendations to improve sales and engagement.

Senior IP Consultant

Sept 2013 - Sept 2014

Responsible for Industrial Design, Patent and Copyright portfolio management.

Trademark Consultant

Apr 2013 - Sept 2013

Providing customers support for their trademark processes and management of their portfolio.

Education

2023 - Web Development Bootcamp (PERN)

· School of Code, Birmingham, UK

2012 - Postgraduate in Innovation Management

· University of Cantabria, Spain

2011 - Bachelors in Business Administration

· University of Cantabria, Spain